<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Jordan Horse Tours on Jordan Horses</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to Jordan Horse Tours on Jordan Horses</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Half-Day Private Indiana Jones Petra Back Road Trial Tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/options_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/options_1/</guid>
      <description>Horse riding inside Petra structures and mountains is splendid experience which the tourist ever had. The back trial is unique because we will start it at little Petra which is unforgettable attraction site which leads to more exquisite places inside the old city Petra. Like the Monastery which is greatest and largest place in Petra. There will be a stunning view to mountains for Jordan and the west bank. The traveler will see the best view in the world there. Will be back to other site in Petra such as the theater, Royal tombs, and treasury the traveler will explore these place closely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horse Riding Tour in Petra-tomb Haroun Trial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/options_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/options_2/</guid>
      <description>This is unique tour inside Petra, the travelers will not force to walk for long distances. we have certified horses the travelers can ride it and start his tour easily.&#xA;Moreover the travelers can see all the sites inside Petra while they ride the horses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana-Jones Archeological Trail Tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/options_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/options_3/</guid>
      <description>What is unique about this tour is that you get to experience Petra from a different point of view, as you will be entering the ancient city via a different trail rather than using the main trail  &lt;em&gt;Al Siq&lt;/em&gt;, and you have the ability to explore &lt;em&gt;Al Siq&lt;/em&gt; on your way back, this will grant you chance to explore almost 80% of Archeological park in one day. I have the ability to explain the history of the ancient city of Petra. and I provide a comprehensive Maps the show many Archaeological marks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
