<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jordan Horses - Options And Prices on Jordan Horses</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jordan Horses - Options And Prices on Jordan Horses</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3-Night 4-Day Wadi Araba Desert Horseback Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/four-day-desertcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/four-day-desertcamp/</guid>
      <description>This unforgettable multi-day adventure takes you deep into the golden sands of the Wadi Araba desert. Ride Arabian horses across breathtaking landscapes, enjoy traditional Bedouin hospitality, and witness desert sunsets and nights. Perfect for adventurous travelers looking to immerse themselves in the natural beauty of southern Jordan and build a close connection with their horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Day Horseback Tour inside Petra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/full-day-insidepetra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/full-day-insidepetra/</guid>
      <description>This unique experience lets you explore many of Petra’s marvelous landmarks on horseback. Combine a visit to Jordan’s number one attraction with a scenic horse ride. Over the course of a full day, you’ll discover the front section of Petra in a truly memorable way. Join us for a beautiful adventure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-Day Little Petra Tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/full-day-littlepetra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/full-day-littlepetra/</guid>
      <description>Horse riding inside Petra&amp;rsquo;s structures and mountains is a splendid experience unlike any other. This unique back trail begins in Little Petra — an unforgettable attraction — and leads to breathtaking sites such as the Monastery, the largest monument in Petra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Day Indiana Jones Archaeological Trail Tour in Petra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/half-day-indianajones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordanhorses/options/half-day-indianajones/</guid>
      <description>This unique tour offers a fresh perspective on Petra by taking you off the main tourist trail. Instead of entering through the usual path of Al Siq, you&amp;rsquo;ll begin on a scenic horseback journey through a lesser-known archaeological route. After the ride, you&amp;rsquo;ll walk back through the famous Siq on foot. You can explore nearly 80% of Petra&amp;rsquo;s archaeological park in a single day.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
